Terms and Privacy Policy for:
=============================

videosmaller.com

By using, browsing and visiting videosmaller.com ("this service", "our service", "this website", "our website") and all its services, you agree with the privacy policy, terms and conditions herein. This End-User License Agreement ("EULA", "agreement") is a legal and forever binding agreement between you (either an individual or a single entity) and our company (the authors of this website). If you do not agree to the terms and policies of this EULA, you are not permitted to use our website and its services in any way and you must discontinue their use immediately.

### Log Files

Our web service might log the IP address of users that visit our website to generate statistics about the service usage and to respond to abuse. The web server might log also other information sent by your web browser, such as the web page visited, the user-agent string, the web browser version, the referer, and so on (read more on [Apache HTTP Server's Log Files Section](http://httpd.apache.org/docs/1.3/logs.html)). We are not interested about who you are, we just log these information for statistical purposes and for security reasons.

### Data Disclosure

Any violations of our terms of use might result in the disclosure of the data recorded in our logs, including (but not limited to) your IP address, to an appropriate third party, which might include, without limitation, law enforcement agencies, child protection agencies or court officials. We might also be required, by law, to provide logs of our service and if requested, such data might be disclosed. In the event that we believe the user has commited a unethical activity (of any kind), we might disclose the data recorded in our log files. You hereby acknowledge and agree that we are permitted to make such disclosure.

### Web Cookies

This website might store cookies on your computer, if allowed by your web browser's privacy settings (for more info on configuring your browser, check AboutCookies.org or read the documentation of your web browser). The cookies used by this websites are used to uniquely identify you to the server and allow our website to remember your preferences, login sessions and recommend you useful web pages and products, these cookies are required for the correct functionality of our website. We may also integrate third-party services (for example Google Analytics, Google AdSense, Social Plugins, etc) that may store their cookies on your web browser and may collect information about your use of our website or other information you’ve provided to them or they’ve collected from your use of their services.

### Analytics Services

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators. Read more details about [Google Analytics terms and privacy policy](https://www.google.com/intl/policies/policies/privacy/).

### Third-party Advertising

This website uses third-party advertising companies (such as Google AdSense by Google Inc.) to serve ads when you visit our website. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website or other websites. Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our website and/or other sites on the Internet. This website uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of our website and user behavior concerning ads, products and the services we offer. You might decide to [disable all the Doubleclick Cookies](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en) if you need to. For more information, please check the privacy policies of the relevant advertisement services that we use:

### Social Network Buttons

Our website uses social networks share buttons and social networks plugins (or widgets) to encourage users to share our website on social networks and to encourage users to communicate with our social pages. These type of services might store cookies on your computer and might still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when you do not use it. Data collected by these services might include your IP address, web pages shared on social networks, and more usage data. To know what data is collected by these services, please check the privacy policies of these services we use:

* [\[Privacy Policy\] AddToAny Share Buttons](https://www.addtoany.com/privacy)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] Twitter Share Button](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170514)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] Facebook Widgets](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

### Third-party Services

This website might integrate third-party services to improve the usability, the page load speed and the service functionality. These third-party services might store cookies on your computer, collect usage data (such as your IP address, details about your web browser), and more. Below we have created a list of all the other third-party web services, subprocessors and applications, that might be used by this website, along with their respective privacy policy. So you can easily read more information about how they collect usage data and how they use web cookies:

* [\[Privacy Policy\] Google Services](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] CDNJS FOSS CDN (MaxCDN)](https://www.maxcdn.com/legal/)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] BootstrapCDN (CloudFlare)](http://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] Amazon Affiliation (Amazon)](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_rel_topic?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] OptinMonster Popups](https://optinmonster.com/privacy/)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] Disqus Comments (Disqus)](https://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] Avangate Affiliate](http://www.avangate.com/privacy.php)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] Sendinblue (Newsletter)](https://www.sendinblue.com/legal/privacypolicy/)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] SendGrid](https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] Google Cloud Platform](https://cloud.google.com/security/compliance?hl=en)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] Scaleway Servers](https://www.scaleway.com/)
* [\[Privacy Policy\] Cryptlex](https://docs.cryptlex.com/legal)

### Files Uploaded

All files uploaded in this web service are automatically deleted after a few hours. Also all the files that have been converted or processed by our web service are automatically deleted after a few hours. Please do not ask us to recover a file you have uploaded or converted with our web service, we can't do that because all the files uploaded and processes by our service are automatically deleted. We have no way to recover or restore them from our web server after they have been successfully deleted. You acknowledge and agree that our system administrators might access or analyze the files for security reasons, and that in some cases the automatic deletion of the files may fail.

### Email Newsletter

We might offer you the possibility to subscribe to our mailing list or email newsletter so we can keep you updated with news and updates about our web services (we might promote also third-party services or products occasionally). To manage the newsletter and the email campaigns we use Sendinblue (read more information about [Sendinblue privacy policy](https://www.sendinblue.com/legal/privacypolicy/)). When you subscribe to our newsletter, your IP address and your email address are sent to the Sendinblue platform via their API service. Your email address will not be shared with third-parties outside of our company, except in case the website or our company are sold. You can unsubscribe from the newsletter at anytime.

### Servers Locations

We use third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run our services and websites. We might use servers and VPS located in Europe (i.e. Italy, France, Germany, the Netherlands) but also servers and VPS located in other states (i.e. United States of America, Canada, etc). You acknowledge and agree that log files and other data (including your IP address, the web pages of our website that you have visited, the user-agent string) and other processed data might be saved in these servers.

### Indemnification

This website (and its services) is provided "as-is" without any kind of expressed warranty, use this website at your own risk. In no event shall the authors, or any other person or company that work at or owns the website, be liable for any consequential, incidental, direct, indirect, special, punitive, or other damages whatsoever (including, without limitation, damages for loss of profits, business interruption, loss of information, or other pecuniary loss) arising out of this agreement or the use of or inability to use this service, even if the sole authors of this service have been advised of the possibility of such damages.

### Service Usage

You agree to not damage, flood or attack this website and you agree to not use this website for purposes unethical, illegal, malicious or illicit, or for any end which could be prejudicial to the authors. You undertake to refrain from illicitly or fraudulently obtaining site contents or stealing or copying said contents. You agree to not use this website and its services if its functionality is prohibited by law in the country where you are located. Any use of our services for purposes that infringe on a copyright is strictly prohibited. When you upload a file on our website you automatically guarantee that you are the legal owner of the file or that you have a legal right to upload and to modify the file. We cannot control how this service is utilized and what kind of files are uploaded in our service, you are the sole responsible about how you use this service.

### More Usage Rules

You must not use our website, and its services for any unlawful activity, including but not limited to viewing illegal content, sharing copyrighted Intellectual Property, or sending threatening, harrassing or abusive email. You agree to not access webmail services for the purpose of sending spam or unsolicited email. You agree to not access bank or credit-card websites. You cannot use or mention our website to compare other websites, services or products. You agree to not abuse, damage or attempt to gain unauthorised access to any website using our website or its services. This includes but it is not limited to, bypassing any restrictions that other webmasters may have put in place against your IP address and accessing content that is unavailable in your country, PC, office or blocked by your ISP.

### External Links

This website contains links to third-party websites or services and may recommend to buy or use external services. This website is not responsible for web pages linked to its websites, and will not therefore be responsible for the contents present on any of such website. You browse such web pages expressely at their own risk, under their own terms, conditions and legal notices for which this website is absolutely not responsible. Moreover, this website assumes no responsibility for the content published on its pages. Some content present on this website may be automatically generated based on user behavior or by scripts.

### Applicable Laws

Our company has headquartes in Italy. This End-User License Agreement (including the privacy policy and the terms of service wrote in this page) is governed by the laws of Italy. Any dispute arising from this agreement and/or its interpretation shall be exclusive competence of the Tribunal of Perugia (PG), Italy, except in the case of matters reserved to the jurisdiction of the Specialized Sections in Intellectual Property: in this case the only competent court will be Florence (FI), Italy.

### No Warranties

We do our best to provide a service that works efficiently and without errors. We strive to provide support via email when possible and to show always accurate information on our services. However, any services provided on this website are provided "as is" without any kind of warranty. We do not guarantee their availability, accuracy, completeness, or the availability of support related to them. We might add, change, remove or discontinue the services provided without any kind of notice.

### Policy Changes

We reserve the right to change these terms and conditions at any time and without prior notice. In the event that any changes are made, the revised terms and conditions shall be posted on this web page immediately. Please check the latest information posted herein to inform yourself of any changes. Feel free to contact us via email if you have any questions.

### Account Registration

When you register to our websites, services or products, we might store some information if required, such as your email address, but except where expressely written, we should never request you to insert personally identificable information or other sensitive information (i.e. surname, address, etc). We might transfer information about you if our websites, services or products are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you by email before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### How we store Passwords

All our registration and login systems use salted password hashing. When you create an account to our service, product or website, the password is stored in the database using a secure hash algorithm (not MD5) and we use different salts to protect your password from being cracked. At no point is the plain-text (unencrypted) password ever written to the hard drive. We recommend to use a long password because most short passwords can easily be cracked, a password of at least 12 or better 15+ characters is much harder to crack, of course you should include also special characters and symbols.

### Your Email Address

If you are required to provide your email address for registering to our services and/or websites, it might be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your account, to send you promotions that might be interested to you, and to send you news about the services and websites related to our Company. In addition, you might receive occasional Company news, updates, related products or services information, coupon codes and promotions about our (and third-party) services, etc.

### How we handle Payments

We do not process payments directly, if you are required to pay a subscription or to buy a product, you acknowledge and agree that we use trusted third-party services that securely handle payments, orders and invoices. We use Bright Market, LLC d/b/a FastSpring as our ecommerce solution, read more information about [FastSpring privacy policy](http://fastspring.com/privacy).
